pepperjam.com 2013-07-02

# Privacy Policy | PepperJam Exchange

## Your Privacy

We at Pepperjam Network value the trust of our members above all else, and we are absolutely committed to keeping that trust by treating the information of our users with the utmost respect. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about the information we collect from our users and how we use and disclose this information. All information you submit to The Pepperjam Network will be held by us and subject to this Privacy Policy.

By accepting Pepperjam Network’s User Agreement, you are consenting to the practices and policies described in this Privacy Policy, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Minor’s Privacy

Pepperjam Network does not target, and is not intended to be used by anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, your use of The Pepperjam Network should be governed by a parent or guardian. Anyone under the age of 18 may not submit any personally identifiable information, and if we discover we have inadvertently gathered any such information, appropriate steps will be taken to delete it.

### The Information We Collect

**Information Given to Us by You**

To use many of the features offered on Pepperjam Network, you will be required to submit certain personally identifiable information such as your name and email address which will be stored by us. We may also obtain information about you in ways other than those specifically described in this policy including any contact with customer care representatives.

**Automatically Gathered Information**

Pepperjam Network, like many other sites, uses “cookies” to obtain information when you access our website. Cookies are small data files that are stored on an Internet user’s computer by a web server. One important use of cookies is to help identify you while you are shopping on our site. The information we collect from cookies and web server logs is used to administer our services and create more of a personalized experience to our users.

Pepperjam Network also gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes the internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, operating system, internet service provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and clickstream data. Use of this information includes: analyzing trends, administration of the site, and tracking of user movements around the web site to gather demographic information.

Pepperjam Network, certain third parties who host portions of our web site, and certain advertising affiliates or others employ cookies and/or small pieces of code known as “web beacons” or “clear gifs” that, on an anonymous basis, count users that have visited a page on our site. We use web beacons to help us better manage content on our site and to determine what is most effective in creating the best possible user experience. Additionally, third party advertising affiliates and others may use the same technology to help track the effectiveness of our advertisements placed on other web sites. Web beacons on our site are not used to collect personally identifiable information about our users. Also, we use web beacons in our emails to let us know which emails our recipients have been opened so that we may gauge how effective our communications are. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see our “Decision to Opt-Out” section.

If you have chosen to receive marketing messages from us about our products and services, we may use information from our log files, cookies or web beacons to help us make those communications more useful or interesting to you.

**Use and Sharing of Information**

Information you provide Pepperjam Network is used by us to offer the best user experience possible, communicate with our users, and generally operate the website.

### Special Offers

Occasionally we may send special offers through email newsletters to users who have chosen to receive such emails from us, on behalf of participating merchants. None of your personally identifiable information is shared with these merchants.

If you wish to opt-out of these newsletters, you may do so by emailing us at privacy@pepperjamnetwork or by mail at:

Pepperjam Network  
7 South Main St – Floor 3  
Wilkes-Barre, Pa 18701  
Business Transaction Disclosures

As our company grows and evolves, we may be involved with certain business transactions such as mergers and acquisitions. Pepperjam Network may be acquired by another company, or transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets within a merger, reorganization, or sale of assets. Under these circumstances it is possible that a merging or acquiring company will gain ownership of the personally identifiable information we have collected.

### Protection

We will disclose information when we believe that it is required by law or we have a good-faith belief that disclosure of this information is necessary to comply with the law, when we are protecting the rights, property, or security Pepperjam Network, its users, employees, or the public, and to assist in fraud protection or investigation.

Pepperjam Network and our licensees reserve the right to republish your content as expressed in our User Agreement. We will use your blog comments and review ratings to personalize site views and feature popular members.

### Links to Other Websites

Pepperjam Network contains links to other websites. We are in no way responsible for the privacy policies or terms of use for these other sites. If you should have concerns about the manner in which other sites gather and use personally identifiable information, be sure to read that site’s privacy policy.

### Security

Pepperjam Network uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We use this to ensure your information during transmission. We also use a secure server hosting location, firewall protection, controlled access and encryption technology to protect your data. The Pepperjam Network takes the security of your personal information very seriously, and our security measures are designed to protect that information in a responsible manner.

### Anti-Spam Policy

Pepperjam Network is 100% opposed to unsolicited commercial email or spam. We do not send emails to anyone without permission and we do not sell or provide email addresses to any unauthorized third party. If you receive any unsolicited emails from spammers, please be assured that Pepperjam Network did not provide your email addresses to such parties. This does not mean that we can prevent spam from happening on the Internet.

If you believe that you have received an unsolicited email from The Pepperjam Network, contact us at privacy@pepperjamnetwork and we will investigate the issue.

### Editing or Deleting Your Information

Registered users of Pepperjam Network may edit or delete their personal information by accessing their Member Profile. We will implement these changes as quickly as possible; however, updates may not be immediate. We will keep certain information you have deleted in our files in some circumstances to enforce our User Agreement, resolve disputes, and analyze programs.

### Decision to Opt-Out

You may choose to opt-out of providing us with certain information, but this may prevent us from personalizing your service or from you taking advantage of certain Pepperjam Network offers and features.

### Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy issues discussed in this policy, please contact us at privacy@pepperjamnetwork.com and we will do our best to address your concerns. If you would prefer contacting us by mail, we may be reached at:

Pepperjam Network  
7 South Main St – Floor 3  
Wilkes-Barre, Pa 18701

### Revisions

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The Pepperjam Network strongly suggests that you check this page regularly to stay on top of any changes made to this policy.
## Your Privacy

We at Pepperjam Network value the trust of our members above all else, and we are absolutely committed to keeping that trust by treating the information of our users with the utmost respect. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about the information we collect from our users and how we use and disclose this information. All information you submit to The Pepperjam Network will be held by us and subject to this Privacy Policy.

By accepting Pepperjam Network’s User Agreement, you are consenting to the practices and policies described in this Privacy Policy, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Minor’s Privacy

Pepperjam Network does not target, and is not intended to be used by anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, your use of The Pepperjam Network should be governed by a parent or guardian. Anyone under the age of 18 may not submit any personally identifiable information, and if we discover we have inadvertently gathered any such information, appropriate steps will be taken to delete it.

### The Information We Collect

**Information Given to Us by You**

To use many of the features offered on Pepperjam Network, you will be required to submit certain personally identifiable information such as your name and email address which will be stored by us. We may also obtain information about you in ways other than those specifically described in this policy including any contact with customer care representatives.

**Automatically Gathered Information**

Pepperjam Network, like many other sites, uses “cookies” to obtain information when you access our website. Cookies are small data files that are stored on an Internet user’s computer by a web server. One important use of cookies is to help identify you while you are shopping on our site. The information we collect from cookies and web server logs is used to administer our services and create more of a personalized experience to our users.

Pepperjam Network also gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes the internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, operating system, internet service provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and clickstream data. Use of this information includes: analyzing trends, administration of the site, and tracking of user movements around the web site to gather demographic information.

Pepperjam Network, certain third parties who host portions of our web site, and certain advertising affiliates or others employ cookies and/or small pieces of code known as “web beacons” or “clear gifs” that, on an anonymous basis, count users that have visited a page on our site. We use web beacons to help us better manage content on our site and to determine what is most effective in creating the best possible user experience. Additionally, third party advertising affiliates and others may use the same technology to help track the effectiveness of our advertisements placed on other web sites. Web beacons on our site are not used to collect personally identifiable information about our users. Also, we use web beacons in our emails to let us know which emails our recipients have been opened so that we may gauge how effective our communications are. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see our “Decision to Opt-Out” section.

If you have chosen to receive marketing messages from us about our products and services, we may use information from our log files, cookies or web beacons to help us make those communications more useful or interesting to you.

**Use and Sharing of Information**

Information you provide Pepperjam Network is used by us to offer the best user experience possible, communicate with our users, and generally operate the website.

### Special Offers

Occasionally we may send special offers through email newsletters to users who have chosen to receive such emails from us, on behalf of participating merchants. None of your personally identifiable information is shared with these merchants.

If you wish to opt-out of these newsletters, you may do so by emailing us at privacy@pepperjamnetwork or by mail at:

Pepperjam Network  
7 South Main St – Floor 3  
Wilkes-Barre, Pa 18701  
Business Transaction Disclosures

As our company grows and evolves, we may be involved with certain business transactions such as mergers and acquisitions. Pepperjam Network may be acquired by another company, or transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets within a merger, reorganization, or sale of assets. Under these circumstances it is possible that a merging or acquiring company will gain ownership of the personally identifiable information we have collected.

### Protection

We will disclose information when we believe that it is required by law or we have a good-faith belief that disclosure of this information is necessary to comply with the law, when we are protecting the rights, property, or security Pepperjam Network, its users, employees, or the public, and to assist in fraud protection or investigation.

Pepperjam Network and our licensees reserve the right to republish your content as expressed in our User Agreement. We will use your blog comments and review ratings to personalize site views and feature popular members.

### Links to Other Websites

Pepperjam Network contains links to other websites. We are in no way responsible for the privacy policies or terms of use for these other sites. If you should have concerns about the manner in which other sites gather and use personally identifiable information, be sure to read that site’s privacy policy.

### Security

Pepperjam Network uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We use this to ensure your information during transmission. We also use a secure server hosting location, firewall protection, controlled access and encryption technology to protect your data. The Pepperjam Network takes the security of your personal information very seriously, and our security measures are designed to protect that information in a responsible manner.

### Anti-Spam Policy

Pepperjam Network is 100% opposed to unsolicited commercial email or spam. We do not send emails to anyone without permission and we do not sell or provide email addresses to any unauthorized third party. If you receive any unsolicited emails from spammers, please be assured that Pepperjam Network did not provide your email addresses to such parties. This does not mean that we can prevent spam from happening on the Internet.

If you believe that you have received an unsolicited email from The Pepperjam Network, contact us at privacy@pepperjamnetwork and we will investigate the issue.

### Editing or Deleting Your Information

Registered users of Pepperjam Network may edit or delete their personal information by accessing their Member Profile. We will implement these changes as quickly as possible; however, updates may not be immediate. We will keep certain information you have deleted in our files in some circumstances to enforce our User Agreement, resolve disputes, and analyze programs.

### Decision to Opt-Out

You may choose to opt-out of providing us with certain information, but this may prevent us from personalizing your service or from you taking advantage of certain Pepperjam Network offers and features.

### Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy issues discussed in this policy, please contact us at privacy@pepperjamnetwork.com and we will do our best to address your concerns. If you would prefer contacting us by mail, we may be reached at:

Pepperjam Network  
7 South Main St – Floor 3  
Wilkes-Barre, Pa 18701

### Revisions

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The Pepperjam Network strongly suggests that you check this page regularly to stay on top of any changes made to this policy.
